interactiveavenues.com 2018-06-12

# Online Marketing Company - Digital Media, SEO, SEM, SMO Agency in India - Interactive Avenues

This privacy policy describes how Interactive Avenues Pvt. Ltd. (“Company”) uses and protects the information that you give to the Company while using this website.

This Privacy Policy is as per the Indian Information Technology Act, 2000 and the Information Technology (Reasonable security and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011 prescribed thereunder, (“Applicable Law”) that is intended to provide visitors to our website with clear and complete information about the data and information that we collect in connection with our Services and the way that data and information is stored and used by our Company. 

##### Information We Collect

Non-Personal Information Collected by our website: Our website may collect "click stream data" related to your visit to our website. Click stream data is anonymous and can include information such as your IP address, Operating System details, Browser details, , the date and time at which those pages were viewed and interaction with content and advertisements on those web pages. Technologies used to collect this click stream data may include cookies and web beacons.

We purge the IP address and irreversibly obfuscate the cookie ID from our log files as soon as we believe this information is no longer required by us.

Personal Information Collected by our website: Primary purpose of collecting personal data on our website is for communication purposes. For example, we may ask you for your contact details for correspondence purposes. We may, from time to time, contact you to provide information about new services that we introduce or receive your feedback on the services rendered. In any event, we will only obtain information from you that is “fit for purpose” and does not constitute an invasion of privacy.

The company reserves the right to retain an archival record of all such correspondence.

We reserve the right to disclose personal data or information you have disclosed to us in response to any judicial process or court order or to provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation of matters related to public safety, as permitted by Applicable Law. In addition, your non-personal information and your personal data or information shall be shared, without obtaining prior consent from you, with Government agencies mandated under the Applicable Law to obtain information for the purpose of verification of identity, or to prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, prosecution and punishment of offences.

##### Cookies:

Our website uses cookies to understand how you use our website. A cookie is a small text file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer, if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. We do not receive any personally identifiable information about you from the cookies that we use. We use analytical/performance cookies which allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. We may also use functionality cookies to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).

You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them in the table below:

Cookie name | Purpose | Expiration  
---|---|---  
_utma | These are analytics cookies managed by a third party that help the Company measure site performance and understand what interests visitors. The Company does not record any information that could identify visitors. | 2 years  
_utmb | These are analytics cookies managed by a third party that help the Company measure site performance and understand what interests visitors. The Company does not record any information that could identify visitors. | 30 minutes  
_utmz | 6 months  
  
Most browsers automatically accept cookies from websites. If you go into your browser settings you can choose to refuse all or some cookies. However, if you set your browser settings to block all cookies you may not be able to access all or parts of our website.

**Information Security:** We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against unauthorized access to, destruction or disclosure of data. This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic and management activities required to protect data integrity, access and use. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential and is not made generally available to the public. Our servers are protected by firewalls and are located in secure data facilities to further increase security. Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal data or information at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.

**Transfer of Information Upon Change of Control:** In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets of our business through a consolidation, merger, asset, purchase or other transaction, we reserve the right to transfer all data (including any personal data or information) that is in our possession or under our control to such acquiring party and thereafter the Privacy Policy of such acquiring party shall govern all such data and any personal data or information that is transferred to the acquiring party.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:** We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated version on this page. The date on which the current Privacy Policy was posted will always be noted at the top of this page. Any change we make to our Privacy Policy will be made in compliance with Applicable Law.

**Correspondence:** If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence, including your email address. This relates to your correspondence with us only - we do not gather users' email addresses as part of our online agency business.

**Questions and Comments:** Questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to or mailed to: [privacy@interactiveavenues.com](mailto:privacy@interactiveavenues.com)
